http://www.ksmnet.org/about-us/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
KSIMC Birmingham
Mehfil e Abbas
Search ...
Search
Saturday, 10 October 2020   22. Safar 1442
17 Clifton Road, Birmingham, B12 8SX Tel: +44(0)121 446 6437Ansaphone: 0121 440 0643secretariat@ksmnet.org
Saturday, 10 October 2020   22. Safar 1442
Sidebar
×
Main Menu
LFAQ Application FormAbout UsHistoryExecutive CommitteeFacilitiesConstitutionKSIMC Strategic PlanComplaints & GrievancesCar Park ProcedureSafeguardingFormsCensus Report 2011-12AccoladesOrganisational StructurePrivacy PolicyNewsLatest UpdatesEventsSub-CommitteesFreecycleWelfare CommitteeHealth & WellbeingCycling GroupChildrens' Tabligh Committee (CTC)Masoomin Sports Club Birmingham Abbasi Youth Network (BAYN)Committee for Social Responsibility (CSR)Clifton Muslim Interfaith (CMI)Building CommitteeInvestmentsAbbasi Islamic Centre ProjectMarriagePre Marriage (BMMF) Post Marriage (Me2We)Burial CommitteeInformationNews of DeathCommunity Cemetery / QabrastanEconomic UpliftmentLoyalty CardBusiness and Occupational DirectoryEducation BoardMuhammadi NurseryMuhammadi Madrasah (Sunday)Muhammadi Madrasah (Saturday)Ladies SectionAz-Zahra Girls ClubAl-Mahdi Boys CrewNewsLadies CommitteeAl-Najiyaat Sports The Book CaveAdult Islamic Education (AIE) [Former AHSN]Az-Zahra Girls ClubResourcesIslam and Shi'aKhoja HistoryVideo Library Video Library Archive Muharram 1436 AH Ashra-e-Zainabiyya 1436 AH Ramadhan 1436 AH Muharram 1437 AH Ashra-e-Zainabiyya 1437 AH Ashra' Zainabiyya 1441 - Urdu/GujratiAshra' Zainabiyya 1441 - EnglishLive Stream
Live Stream - UrduLive Urdu - FlashLive Urdu - MP3Live Urdu - JavaLive Urdu - WMLive Stream - EnglishLive English - FlashLive English - MP3Live English - JavaLive English - WMLive Stream - YouTube Lecture SummariesUseful LinksCOEJ Nasimco World Federation of KSIMC Contact UsKSIMC OfficeWebsite FeedbackDirections Ask our AlimSub Committees
Masoomin Sports ClubMuhammadi MadrasahAbbasi YouthBuilding CommitteeEducation BoardEconomic UpliftmentLadies CommitteeLadies Sports Committee
Live
LFAQ Application Form
About Us
History
Executive Committee
Facilities
Constitution
KSIMC Strategic Plan
Cycling Group
Childrens' Tabligh Committee (CTC)
Masoomin Sports Club
Birmingham Abbasi Youth Network (BAYN)
Committee for Social Responsibility (CSR)
Clifton Muslim Interfaith (CMI)
Building Committee
Investments
Abbasi Islamic Centre Project
Marriage
Pre Marriage (BMMF)
Post Marriage (Me2We)
Burial Committee
Information
News of Death
Community Cemetery / Qabrastan
Economic Upliftment
Loyalty Card
Business and Occupational Directory
Education Board
Muhammadi Nursery
Muhammadi Madrasah (Sunday)
Muhammadi Madrasah (Saturday)
Ladies Section
Az-Zahra Girls Club
Al-Mahdi Boys Crew
News
Ladies Committee
Al-Najiyaat Sports
The Book Cave
Adult Islamic Education (AIE) [Former AHSN]
Az-Zahra Girls Club
Resources
Islam and Shi'a
Khoja History
Video Library
Video Library Archive
Muharram 1436 AH
Ashra-e-Zainabiyya 1436 AH
Remember Me
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
Live
"Creating a spiritual & vibrant community based on the values and practices of the Islamic Shi'a Ithna-Ashari faith by developing the potential of its members, engaging with the wider society and serving the needs of humanity worldwide."
Privacy Policy
Print
Email
Introduction
We rely on your generosity in order to carry out our activities and are therefore committed to be transparent about how we use and securely store your personal details in order to carry out our mission. In conformity with the EU General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), we are committed to storing your data securely and ensuring that it is not violated in any way.
Who are we?
We are the Khoja Shia Ithna-Asheri Muslim Community of Birmingham (KSIMCB) and have existed for over 40 years. We are registered in England and Wales as a CIO under charity number 1170675. For the purposes of the GDPR, the KSIMCB is the data controller.
What information do we collect?
We collect information in the following ways:
Information you give us
For example, when you engage with our social media or message boards, make a donation to us, register for an event or programme, surveys or otherwise provide us with personal information in another form.
Information we get from your use of our website and services
We collect information about the services you use and how you use them. Wherever possible we use aggregated or anonymous information which does not identify individual visitors to our websites. When someone visits our website, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.
Information from third parties
We may also receive information about you from third parties. This can include information such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number, your geographic location (for mobile devices), credit/debit card details and whether you are a tax payer so that we can claim Gift Aid.  We, like all companies, are able to confirm what browser you are using, IP address and computer operating systems that are being used and this information may be used to improve the services we offer
How do we use your information?
We may use your information to:
process a donation that you have made
process orders that you have submitted
carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us
provide services and events to cater for the needs of the Community
seek your views or comments on the services we provide
notify you of changes to our services or any updates
send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you. These may include information about campaigns, appeals, other fundraising activities and promotions
process a loan, grant or job application
We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations (for example the collection of Gift Aid). We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties.
We will not share your information with third parties without your explicit consent.
When you are using our secure online donation pages, your donation is processed by a third party payment processor, who specializes in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions. If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please contact us.
We may transfer your personal information to a third party in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of our supporters and customers. However, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.
Legal Bases
Under the GDPR we must have a legal basis to process your information.
In most cases we collect and process your data with your consent, for example, when you sign up on our website to receive marketing material from us.
Sometimes we need your personal information to comply with our contractual obligations, for example, when you make a donation, we ask for your billing address and card details.
If the Law requires us to, we may need to collect and process your data, for example, when we claim gift aid we send your details to HMRC.
In specific situations, we require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way which might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and which does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests, for example, when we contact you to inform you about the progress of a specific donation you may have made.
Marketing
We will not use your personal information for marketing purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish to be contacted by us for such purposes. However, we will retain your details on a suppression list to help ensure that we do not continue to contact you.
Access to your information and correction
You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold. You also have a right to restrict how we contact you. Please email your request to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
You have the right to request a computer file in a common format (e.g. CSV or similar) containing the personal data that you have previously provided to us and the right to have your information transferred to another entity where this is technically possible.
Cookies
We do not use cookies to personally identify anyone. If we use them, it is to enhance your experience when using the website by identifying how it is being used and where we can make improvements. We may also use cookies to monitor how our advertisements perform.
External websites
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to other sites, not owned or managed by us or links to the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change our policy from time to time so please visit our website and read through our privacy policy each time you share your personal information with us.  If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use our website to submit personal information to us.  If material changes are made to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the website.
Prev
Live Stream
Announcements
Hilal Statement - Rabi ul Awwal 1442AH
BAYN Announcement - Karbala Project
Ashra' Zainabiyya Daily Programme
Jamaat Programmes 1442 AH
General Feedback
The EC would like to encourage all members to give feedback on various aspects of the Jamaat.
Please email us with any ideas / suggestions / feedback you may have regarding programmes, future direction etc of the Jamaat.
Any comments are welcome.
You are here: Home
About Us
Privacy Policy
© KHOJA SHIA ITHNA-ASHERI MUSLIM COMMUNITY OF BIRMINGHAM, 17 Clifton Road, Balsall Heath, Birmingham, B12 8SX, Registered Charity in the UK: 1170675.
